IP Lab-1 Mikil Lalwani D15B/37

Aim -

Basics of HTML5, Structure of HTML5 Document.

Explain basic tags and their properties. (text formatting,anchor,img,list tag,tables etc)

Programs:

- (a) To create a personal profile using basic HTML tags.
- (b) Create Marksheet using advanced table tags.

Theory-

- 1. $\langle a \rangle$ for link
- 2. to make bold text
- 3. for bold text with emphasis
- 4. <body> main HTML part
- 5.
br> for break
- 6. <div> it is a division or part of an HTML document
- 7. <h1>... for titles
- 8. <i> to make an italic text
- 9. for images in document
- 10. is an ordered list
- 11. for an unordered list
- 12. is a list item in a bulleted (ordered list)
- 13. for paragraph
- 14. to style part of text
- 15. to create table
- 16. to make a table row
- 17. to display table headers
- 18. to display table data

Screenshots-

Profile



Name - John Eivor

Phone No: 044 412 2020 Palo Alto, CA linkedin.com/in/john.eivor.john-eivor.com

Data Scientist Data Scientist With 4+ years of broad-based experience in building data-intensive applications, overcoming complex architectural, and scalability issues in diverse industries. Proficient in predictive modeling, data processing, and data mining algorithms, as well as scripting languages, including Python and Java. Capable of creating, developing, testing, and deploying highly adaptive diverse services to translate business and functional qualifications into substantial deliverables.

Work Experience

Data Scientist Future Energy Ltd. 06/2018 - Present Palo Alto, CA

- Develop action plans to mitigate risks in decision making while increasing profitability by leveraging data science.

 Drive the interaction and partnership between the managers to ensure active cooperation in identifying as well as defining analytical needs, and generating the pull-through of insights with the business.

 Build predictive models using various machine learning tools to predict the possibility of equipment failure

 Develop algorithms using Natural Language Processing and Deep Learning models for predictive maintenance.

- Utilized analytical and technical expertise to provide insights and proposals to support business improvements.
 Evaluated analytical model findings in the Global Monitoring Report, the company's flagship product.
 Conducted business analysis to understand business needs and requirements to translate into conceptual designs.
 Actively engaged in the quantitative analysis of sophisticated modeling to address business issues.

Business Analyst / Statistician Maxicare Healthcare 02/2013 - 12/2015 San Francisco, CA

- Conducted business process analysis and identified critical issues, gaps, and needs for an established process center.

 Developed Key Performance Indicators (KPI) and presented it to the management and led to the execution plan.

 Analyzed and produced KPI reports allowing to monitor field service engineer and customer care center closely. Led training sessions on the software developed and presented it to the management for approval of deployment.

Education

Master of Science in Computer Science and Informatics San Francisco University 2014 - 2016

General Skills

Skill	Proficiency		
Data Visualization	High		
Machine Learning	High		
Deep Learning	Medium		
Pattern Recognition	Low		
Database Structures & Algorithms	Medium		
Statistical Analytis	High		
Data Preparation	High		
Quality Management	Low		
Agile Methodologies	Medium		

Technical Skills

Operating System: Windows, MacOS, Limix
Database/Server: My SQL, Postgres, SQL Server
Programming Language: Python, scikil-learn, Python, OpenCV, D3.js, H20.ai, Spark, Hadoop, R Programming, Django, Angular.js, HTML, SQL, JavaScript, PHP
Other Software/Tools: Tableau, Deep Learning, Machine Learning, IP Cameras, AWS Services, Microsoft Azure

Marksheet

Student Details Subjects			Total	0			
Roll Number	Name	BlockChain	CyberSecurity	Data Science	Industrial Management	lotai	Out Of
101	Hilmar Aiello	88	62	81	68	301	
102	Iqaluk Wragge	65	57	53	74	249	
103	Marie-Christine Chaput	82	62	78	89	311	400
104	Filippa Bolívar	65	56	61	85	267	400
105	Flora Ewart	80	92	62	85	319	
	Average	76	66	67	81	290	

Conclusion-

We have successfully created a personal profile and mark sheet.